<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-07-18T09:42:00-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Tools of The Trade</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/tools-of-the-tradet/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/tools-of-the-tradet/</id>
    <published>2015-07-18T09:42:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-18T10:30:15-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Technology plays an integral part of my daily routine. As such, I wanted to put together a list of tools and applications I use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="applications-i-trust"&gt;Applications I trust&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://slack.com"&gt; Slack&lt;/a&gt; - If you've ever had a productive meeting with your team, but have had trouble maintaining that momentum and energy, give this app a shot. It provides organization and structure to real time communication unlike anything else I've tested. A must have tool for creative collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://evernote.com"&gt; Evernote&lt;/a&gt; - Keyword is convenience. When a Kramer-style "mental note" won't suffice, I turn to Evernote. Notes that travel with you wherever you go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://furbo.org/2013/06/28/the-origin-of-tweet/"&gt; Twitterific&lt;/a&gt; - The ORIGINAL Twitter Client and my app of choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://dropbox.com"&gt; Dropbox&lt;/a&gt; - The only storage system I trust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.noisli.com/"&gt; Noisli&lt;/a&gt; - When podcasts &amp;amp; music are too distracting, I use this app for natural sound. My preference is waves crashing :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://atom.io/"&gt; Atom for Mac&lt;/a&gt; - My current text editor of choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photoshop - Mainly used for Deck making, Image optimizing, and mock layouts. Still haven't made the jump to Sketch app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terminal - I still rock the command line cuz I'm old school.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Mid Year Review</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/mid-year-self-assessment-of-goals/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/mid-year-self-assessment-of-goals/</id>
    <published>2015-06-19T22:57:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-07T22:27:36-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Already July. Wow. Time sure flies when you're having fun, or maybe it just flies when life happens all at once. Seems as good a time as ever to take a step back and take a look at what's transpired so far in 2015 and what's to come for the remainder of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the start of the year, Kam (my amazing girlfriend) and I decided to put together a list of goals we wanted to reach. Our lists varied from getting involved in a local charity, to entrepreneurial efforts, athletic achievements and more. All in all it was a fairly standard but ambitious set of goals, but hey who doesn't want to accomplish everything in a year? Lists are great. They force you to think big picture. They help you focus on the important things in life. I encourage everyone to create lists, so long as they follow two rules:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) Follow-through. Don't just write it down because it looks good. Make sure it's something you feel a serious connection to, and go do it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) Progress over results. Depending on the ambition, there's a high likelihood you're going to reach all of your goals in a single year. It takes time, so remember to be patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took a look at my list this week and I'm not gonna lie, there's still plenty of work to be done. One goal I have been able to reach, however, is traveling abroad with Kam. We were lucky enough to visit Paris, Barcelona and Mallorca. It was truly an amazing and unforgettable trip. Honestly don't think I've ever eaten so much food in my life before. I wish we had a few more extra days to travel around, especially in Paris. We're already planning our return trip back! Here's a few iphone pics from our travels:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="/images/./IMG_6336.JPG" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="post-thumb"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="/images/./IMG_6342.JPG" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure class="post-thumb"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="/images/./2015-05-21-21.26.13-1.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure class="post-thumb"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="/images/./IMG_6327.JPG" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure class="post-thumb"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="/images/./IMG_6326.JPG" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love to travel. I feel like every time I leave my little bubble in Venice, I'm able to see things through a different lens, a different perspective. And most importantly, it allows me time to think about the important things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I glance over at my list of Goals today, I can see that most of it has not been accomplished. Some of it hasn't been touched. But the important thing is that there is PROGRESS being made. I haven't been able to read one book per month, but I've read a few books and it's started to become a weekly habit again. I haven't yet volunteered at a local organization, but I've made contact and the wheels are in motion for that to start happening this summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm sure all my goals will not come to fruition in 5 months time, but I am excited to see what I'm able to get done from now until December. Day by day, week by week, I plan to hold myself accountable and make the effort. No excuses.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>2015 MadburyClub.com Redesign</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/tmc-redesign/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/tmc-redesign/</id>
    <published>2015-06-10T11:37:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-07T22:36:56-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Since its inception in early 2010, The Madbury Club's digital presence has evolved at the same frenetic pace as its work. It started out as a blog. Then it became a music review site. Then Spreads. Then Editorial pieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In its current iteration, most of the recent content is what you'd see from a Creative Agency, with more of a focus on Client-centric deliveries. I had the opportunity to work with Phillip on the redesign as we migrated from a CMS server-side platform to the Cloud Based, Static Site Generator &lt;a href="http://siteleaf.com"&gt; Siteleaf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="/images/./browser-source-code.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was able to dig up a large number of archived works TMC had produced in the past and give them new life in a responsive layout. Responsibilities included Web Development, Design, Project Management, Development of Tumblr Theme. Visit &lt;a href="http://madburyclub.com"&gt; The Madbury Club &lt;/a&gt; to get the full experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="/images/./browser-source-code-copy.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="mobile" src="/images/./iPhone6a.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Here goes nothing...</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/here-goes-nothing/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/here-goes-nothing/</id>
    <published>2015-06-03T11:29:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-07T22:22:04-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After much tossing and turning, I've decided to take the plunge and invest a chunk of my weekly agenda into this here currently non-existant blog. I read a ton of blogs and sites and have recently felt inspired enough to share my point of view with the world. I mean, it is 2015 right?? If nothing else, it will provide me some time to strengthen my puny writing skills (bare with me, it's going to take some time to find my stride…) Here's what I'd like the focus of my posts to be (These are all subject to change at any given time):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="trophies"&gt;Trophies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last thing I'd want to do is turn this whole endeavor into a boast fest of all my accomplishments. Having said that, I do intend to highlight certain moments or feats of my own that deserve recognition. It could be a  product launch (foreshadowing), it could be a new job, a basket weaving competition, whatever. I'll leave this one open-ended for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="community-involvement"&gt;Community Involvement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's a big part of my list of Goals for 2015, and to ensure that I deliver in full, I will make the effort to also update the blog on all new happenings in this arena. Really feel it's important to give back to my local community and do my part to make it a better place to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="web-development-and-beyond"&gt;Web Development and Beyond!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just the beginning. What lies before you is but a mere responsive/quick/ static foundation. I want to develop my Front End skills further and teach myself a bunch of languages - mainly Ruby, Python, Django, Java, Swift, and more. No better place than to start right here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="life-reckoning"&gt;Life Reckoning&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to stay private, I will keep these posts to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There you have it. Guess it's time to &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2F1bMG9wzXY"&gt; kick the tires and light the fire &lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
